const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "2.9",
    title: "Ordinal Numbers",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "pierwszy",
    back: "first (1st)",
  },
  {
    front: "drugi",
    back: "second (2nd)",
  },
  {
    front: "trzeci",
    back: "third (3rd)",
  },
  {
    front: "czwarty",
    back: "fourth (4th)",
  },
  {
    front: "piąty",
    back: "fifth (5th)",
  },
  {
    front: "szósty",
    back: "sixth (6th)",
  },
  {
    front: "siódmy",
    back: "seventh (7th)",
  },
  {
    front: "ósmy",
    back: "eighth (8th)",
  },
  {
    front: "dziewiąty",
    back: "ninth (9th)",
  },
  {
    front: "dziesiąty",
    back: "tenth (10th)",
  },
  {
    front: "jedenasty",
    back: "eleventh",
  },
  {
    front: "dwunasty",
    back: "twelfth",
  },
  {
    front: "trzynasty",
    back: "thirteenth",
  },
  {
    front: "czternasty",
    back: "fourteenth",
  },
  {
    front: "piętnasty",
    back: "fifteenth",
  },
  {
    front: "szesnasty",
    back: "sixteenth",
  },
  {
    front: "siedemnasty",
    back: "seventeenth",
  },
  {
    front: "osiemnasty",
    back: "eighteenth",
  },
  {
    front: "dziewiętnasty",
    back: "nineteenth",
  },
  {
    front: "dwudziesty",
    back: "twentieth",
  },
  {
    front: "dwudziesty pierwszy",
    back: "twenty-first",
  },
  {
    front: "dwudziesty drugi",
    back: "twenty-second",
  },
  {
    front: "trzydziesty trzeci",
    back: "thirty-third",
  },
  {
    front: "czterdziesty piąty",
    back: "forty-fifth",
  },
  {
    front: "pięćdziesiąty",
    back: "fiftieth",
  },
  {
    front: "sześćdziesiąty pierwszy",
    back: "sixty-first",
  },
  {
    front: "siedemdziesiąty drugi",
    back: "seventy-second",
  },
  {
    front: "osiemdziesiąty czwarty",
    back: "eighty-fourth",
  },
  {
    front: "sto drugi",
    back: "a hundred second",
  },
  {
    front: "tysiąc pierwszy",
    back: "one thousand first",
  },
];

export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
